bondage.com 2007-10-11

# Bondage | Privacy Policy

### Updated 2006-06-18

### Summary

Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Bondage.com will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know.

Please not that this policy applies to Personally Identifiable Information (PII), as well as information collected by Bondage.com in a manner that would reasonably imply privacy. Information which you choose to post on Bondage.com, in your personals profile, blog, the forums, and so on, will indeed be shown to other users of the site, any may be made available to search engines and/or exposed for syndication via RSS.

### Scope

This document replaces all previous documents including to but not limited to previous registration agreements, online registrations, and any other method used or developed to grant access to bondage.com.

This policy applies to all users of Bondage.com. The term "Bondage.com service" defines the total environment, and includes, but is not limited to, the bondage.com web site, IRC network, email system, database, documentation, and content.

### Information Collection and Use

Bondage.com (hereby referred to as "we" in the following policy) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or license this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

### Subscription Data

Bondage.com offers upgraded memberships which require payment. These payments are processed through third party billers, including Netbilling, CCBill, and others. Some information submitted to third party billers may be made available to Bondage.com for administrative purposes. See the privacy policy on the actual payment page for detailed information about the policies of a specific third party biller.

### IP Address and Browser information

Your IP address is used by Bondage.com to record your transactions, as well as diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address and browser information can also be used to identify you to authorities in the case of fraud or illegal activity.

Bondage.com analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on our website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site, except in cases of fraud or abuse. In addition. Bondage.com may contract with third parties for various services, including advertisement serving, content delivery and additional log file analysis. In those cases, selected third parties may have access to IP address and browser information, but again the information is not personally identifiable.

### Resale or disclosure of information to third parties

Bondage.com does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including email addresses, IM addresses, and matchmaker profiles. Customer names will not be sold. We will not share your information with third parties although Bondage.com completely abides by law and will respond to subpoenas, warrants or other court orders regarding information of a particular visitor. Additionally, if a member is believed to be engaged in illegal activity, we reserve the right to report this to law enforcement.

Please note: This section expressly applies to your personal information that we may collect, and not to the actual content of your personals profile and any other information that you choose to make publicly visible on Bondage.com. Of course, if you choose to disclose personal information in your profile or communications with other Bondage.com members, that information will be disclosed to third parties.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. These communications can be handled via an internal @bondage.com address or an external email address, depending on user preference and account configuration, or they can be disabled entirely.

### Correcting / Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as billing information), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
